残酷な天使のように 少年よ 神話になれ
青い風が今 胸のドアを叩いても 私だけをただ見つめて 微笑んでるあなた
そっと触れるもの 求めることに夢中で 運命さえまだ知らない 痛いけな瞳
だけどいつか気づくでしょう その背中には
遥か未来 目指すための羽があること
残酷な天使の帝世 窓辺からやがて飛び立つ
ほとばしる熱いパッドスで 思い出を裏切るなら
この空を抱いて輝く 少年よ 神話になれ
鉄道の関係
メンバー
カードズミッチ
May I have your attention. As of 12.30 p.m. today, a special state of emergency has been declared for the Kanto and Chubu regions surrounding the Tokai district.
All residents must evacuate to their designated shelters immediately. Repeat.
As of 12.30 p.m. today, a state of emergency has been declared for the Kanto and Chubu regions surrounding the Tokai district.
All residents must evacuate to their shelters immediately.
Damn! Why did I have to lose him at a time like this?
Why now?
We're sorry. Due to the state of special emergency, no lines are currently available. This is a recording.
It's no use. This is dumb. I shouldn't have come here.
I guess we won't be meeting here.
Maybe I should find a shelter.
Anything else?
An identified intruder is still coming towards us.
We've got it on visual. I'm putting it on the main screen.
It's been 15 years.
Yes. Well, now we know for sure.
The angels are back.
Every single missile hit the target!
Sorry. Get in. Am I real late?
The target's still coming towards us. It's headed straight for Tokyo 3.
The air defense force doesn't have enough firepower to stop it.
Fire everything we've got! Mobilize the Yatsugi and Iruma forces!
Don't hold anything back! Destroy that thing at any cost!
It's not possible! That was a direct hint!
The tank battalion's been wiped out! Guided missiles and artillery fire seem to have no effect at all!
Damn it! We've hit it with everything we've got and we're not even touching it!
Looks like an AT field.
Yes. Conventional weapons are no match for the angels.
I understand, sir. We'll execute backup plan at once.
Now wait a second!
No! They're going to use an N2 mine!
Get down!
No!
Yeah!
We did it!
Well, Ikari, it looks like you won't be getting a shot at it.
getting a shot at it shockwave approaching are you all right yeah but
my mouth is full of dirt you'll be all right come on ready to push
thanks shinji you're pretty useful thank you but i should thank you miss katsuragi
uh misado is fine so shinji ikari we meet it last uh yeah what's the status of the target
we're unable to confirm the e impulse knocked everything out it must be dead it took the full
blast external sensors restored energy reading at the epicenter it can't be external cameras online
oh what the that was our last resort no effect at all it's a demon
yes don't worry his safety is my top priority look can you get a car train ready for us
an express of course
well i did volunteer to pick him up so it's only my duty to make sure he gets there see ya
oh this stinks i i just had this car repaired and it's a total wreck already 33 more payments to go
plus the cost of repairs and look my favorite dress is ruined ruined and i look so good in it
excuse me misado hmm what's that those batteries isn't that um theft uh don't worry about it uh it's an
emergency and we needed a working car right uh i am a government official after all so everything's
gonna be perfectly fine okay okay i don't think anyone will buy that excuse you're no fun you know
you're not as cute as i thought you were is that so ooh angry i'm sorry you're just a boy after all
you're not as mature as i thought you'd be either
as we suspected it's regenerating itself without that ability it couldn't operate without support
units well quite impressive it can upgrade its operational parameters and it's also getting
smarter it should renew its attack any minute now
the gates are now closing please stand clear this is a v22 special express
it's a secret organization controlled by the u.m this train will bypass where my father works
well yeah you do know what he does don't you
all my teachers told me was that it was important to the future of mankind
command of this operation is being entrusted to you don't betray our trust yes sir mr ikari we've
already seen that our weapons seem to have no effect on these things that's why we're giving you a chance
are you sure that you can beat them that is why nerve exists i pray you're right
the target is still stationary estimated current ability to intercept is only 7.5
percent the wind forces are exhausted what are you going to do activate unit one activate it but we
have no pilot not anymore another spare is being delivered misado are we going to see my father
of course of course of course we are
father
oh yeah did your dad send you an id card
yeah this is it oh thanks
here start reading this okay nerve my father's agency am i going to be working for him
what am i saying he wouldn't have sent me a letter unless he needed me for something
sounds like you don't get along with your dad how you sound just like me
oh
it's a real geo front that's right this is our secret underground base nerve central
this city is the key to rebuilding our world a fortress for all mankind
oh
what on earth isn't this the right way
it's because of these things that i hate to wear a skirt around here
i wonder where in the heck ritsuko is i'm sorry i'm not used to this place
we passed this spot twice already
well don't worry about it they make these transit things to be used you know
with the chairperson of e-project technical division one dr ritsuko akagi please contact
captain misato katsuragi of operations division i don't believe it is she lost again
uh hi there ritsuko
why are you wasting my time captain don't you know we're short on time and manpower sorry
so is this the boy right according to the mar duke report he's the third child
hmm pleased to meet you huh oh sure i'm afraid he's just like his father the gruff and unfriendly
part that is handle the rest of this their first meeting in three years
sir it looks like the target's starting to move again i see let's go to battle stations level one
battle stations level one there we go it sounds pretty serious so how's unit one coming it's
currently undergoing refrigeration using the b type equipment does it really work it's never
worked before has it the possibility of activation is zero point zero zero zero zero zero zero zero one
percent around here we just call it the o-nine system does that mean it doesn't work don't be
insulting it's o-nine as an oni a japanese devil hmm well anyway i suppose it's a bit late to be saying
sorry it doesn't work
hey why is it so dark in here
oh it's a face a giant robot
you won't find this in there what this is man's ultimate fighting machine the synthetic life form
known as evangelion unit one built here in secret it is mankind's last hope
is this my father's work correct
it's been a while father
we're moving out moving out but unit zero still in cryostasis
wait a minute you're gonna use unit one there's no other way now wait rei can't do it yet can she
we don't have a pilot we just received one you're serious shinji akari
you will pilot it huh but even rei anami took seven months to synchronize with her eva it's
impossible for him to do it he just got here he just has to sit in the seat we don't expect more
than that but listen defeating that angel is our ultimate priority if we have someone who has a chance
that synchronizing with an eva then we've got to risk it you do understand that don't you captain katsuragi
yes ma'am
why did you send for me you know why i sent for you so you're asking me to take this thing and go
out there and fight correct how could you do this to me i thought you didn't want me why why did you
have to call me now father because i have a use for you
but why why because there is no one else who can no i can't i've never even seen anything like this
before there's no way i can do this you will be instructed but still there's no way i can't pilot that
do this thing if you're going to do it do it now if not then leave
it's close it must sense us
shinji we don't have much time
get inside yeah this is all wrong i came all this way oh why did i come
why shinji exactly why did you come here you mustn't run away you must confront your father
and you must confront yourself i know that but i just can't
you can't do it
fiyutsuki sir wake up ray can we use her she's not dead yet understood
ray yes our spare is unusable you will do it again yes sir
reconfigure unit one system for ray then activate roger calling off current program
beginning activation i knew it i'm not needed after all
whoo
uh
Huh?
The hava activated itself!
It ripped right out of the right arm restraint!
No! That's not possible!
The entry plug wasn't even inserted!
That just can't happen!
You mean it reacted without any kind of interface?
Was it really to protect something?
To protect him?
It's him.
Oh!
I mustn't run away.
I mustn't run away!
I'll do it.
I'll pilot it!
COOLING PROCESS COMPLETED!
RIGHT ARM REPAIRS COMPLETED!
CAGE NOW IN POSITION FOR DOCKING!
SIGNAL PLUG TERMINATOR NOW BEING EJECTED!
ROGER! INSERTING ENTRY PLUG!
PLUG! LOCKED IN PLACE! CONNECTING UNIT ONE!
WHAT IS THIS STUFF?!
DON'T WORRY! ONCE YOUR LUNGS ARE FILLED WITH LCL, YOUR BLOOD WILL BE OXYGENATED DIRECTLY!
IT'S OKAY! YOU'LL GET USED TO IT!
STOP COMPLAINING! YOU'RE A BOY, YOU KNOW!
CONNECTING MAIN POWER! ALL CIRCUITS TRANSMITTING!
ROGER! CONNECTING SECONDARY CONTACTS!
A10 NERV CONNECTION NORMAL!
CONFIGURE THE LANGUAGE LOGIC INTERFACE FOR JAPANESE!
ALL PRELIMINARY CONTACTS ESTABLISH! PERFORMANCE NOMINAL!
BI-DIRECTIONAL CIRCUITS ARE OPEN!
SYNCHRONIZATION RATIO AT 41.3%!
AMAZING!
HARMONICS SEEMED TO BE NORMAL!
I SEE NO DISTURBANCES!
LET'S DO IT!
BEGIN LAUNCH SEQUENCE!
BEGINNING LAUNCH SEQUENCE!
REMOVING PRIMARY LOCKBOLTS!
REMOVAL CONFIRMED!
REMOVING THE UMBILICAL BRIDGE!
REMOVING SECONDARY LOCKBOLTS!
REMOVING PRIMARY RESTRAINTS!
REMOVING SECONDARY RESTRAINTS!
RELEASING SAFETY LOCKS NUMBER 1 THROUGH 50!
INTERNAL BATTERY FULLY CHARGED!
EXTERNAL BATTERY OUTLET CLOTHED!
ROGER!
MOVE AVA UNIT 1 TO THE LAUNCH PAD!
LAUNCH PATH CLEAR!
ALL SYSTEMS GREEN!
EVANGELION!
READY FOR LAUNCH!
UNDERSTOOD!
CAN WE REALLY DO THIS?
OF COURSE!
UNLESS WE DEFEAT THE ANGELS, WE HAVE NO FUTURE!
VIKARI, ARE YOU ABSOLUTELY CERTAIN?
EVIL LAUNCH!
FIRE!
DECK!
SO WE NEED!
YOU WHO NEED!
GO!
Shinji, don't get killed out there.
Spring is life, I'm too bitter and mild.
In other words, hold my hand.
In other words, darling, kiss me.
Fill my heart with some, and let me sing forevermore.
You are all I long for, all I worship and adore.
In other words, please be true.
In other words, I love you.
The Eva triumphs, but this angel is only the beginning.
Worried about Shinji's mental state, Misato brashly decides to move him in with her.
However, Shinji's mind only becomes more shut off from the rest of the world.
It all happens in the next episode, and I'll be slipping you a little extra as well.